<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<organizations>
    <organization>
        <id>3001</id>     <!--organization_id-->
        <user_id></user_id>
        <category>Music</category>
        <genre>Classical</genre>
        <type>choral</type>
        <name>Wheatland Chorale</name>
        <description>
            The Wheatland Chorale has earned a reputation as one of Pennsylvania's premier choral ensembles. The singers, all volunteers, are selected through audition, and travel from throughout Central and Southeastern Pennsylvania for weekly rehearsals in Lancaster. The Chorale is named for its birthplace in the Wheatland Hills area of Lancaster. The popularity of the Wheatland Chorale has grown steadily. The regular season includes a concert subscription series, performed in Lancaster, Wyomissing and at Elizabethtown College.
        </description>
        <address>
            <street/>
            <box/>
            <city>Lancaster</city>
            <state>PA</state>
            <zipcode/>
        </address>
        <phone/>
        <website>http://www.wheatlandchorale.org/</website>
        <director>Eric Riley</director>
        <artists>
            <artist/>
        </artists>
        <performers>
            <performer/>
        </performers>
        <images>
            <image>
                http://wheatlandchorale.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/wheatland-group2.jpg
            </image>
        </images>
        <audioclips>
            <audio/>
        </audioclips>
    </organization>
    <organization>
        <id>3002</id>
        <type>choral</type>
        <name>Musical Associates</name>
        <description>
            Musical Associates is a select group of singers and instrumentalists, dedicated to bringing the finest in choral music 
            to music lovers in the Susquehanna Valley. Under the direction of Artistic Director Emery DeWitt, the singers and 
            instrumentalists include many of the area's top soloists. Concerts are usually held in the summer.
        </description>
        <address>
            <city>Lancaster</city>
            <state>PA</state>
        </address>
        <phone/>
        <website>http://www.musicalassociates.org/</website>
        <director>Emery DeWitt</director>
        <images>
            <image>
                http://musicalassociates.org/wp/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/MA-Header-weaver-ii-940x324-top-title1.jpg
            </image>
        </images>
    </organization>
    <organization>
        <id>3003</id>
        <type>orchestra</type>
        <name>Lancaster Symphony Orchestra</name>
        <description>
            Now in its 66th season, the Lancaster Symphony Orchestra has played for over three decades under the direction of 
            Maestro Stephen Gunzenhauser. The Symphony has evolved from a community orchestra playing a few concerts per year 
            into a $1.7 million organization of professional musicians presenting six Classic Series concerts, the Sounds of 
            the Season holiday concert series and two New Year's Celebration concerts. The concerts feature international 
            guest artists and conductors and frequent U.S. and world premieres, such as 2012's national premiere of 
            Disney's Fantasia Live In Concert. Opening Night Friday audiences are also treated to a post-concert reception 
            where they can interact with the Symphony's musicians and guest artists.
        </description>
        <address>
            <street>226 North Arch Street</street>
            <box/>
            <city>Lancaster</city>
            <state>PA</state>
            <zipcode>17603</zipcode>
        </address>
        <phone>717-291-6440</phone>
        <website>http://www.lancastersymphony.org/</website>
        <director>Stephen Gunzenhauser</director>
        <images>
            <image>http://www.witf.org/center-stage/LSO_orchestra_Gunzenhauser%2520resized%2520homepg.jpg</image>
        </images>
    </organization>
    <organization>
        <id>3004</id>
        <type>orchestra</type>
        <name>Allegro - the Chamber Orchestra of Lancaster</name>
        <description>
            Allegro means joyful … fast and lively … a different musical experience … We invite you to experience the joy 
            of Allegro! Allegro brings the music to life through concerts that are specially designed to be engaging, 
            enjoyable and fun. Our musicians clearly love what they are doing. The players mingle with the audience before 
            concerts, during intermission and after performances.
        </description>
        <address>
            <box>P.O. Box 1741</box>
            <city>Lancaster</city>
            <state>PA</state>
            <zipcode>17608</zipcode>
        </address>
        <phone>717-560-7317</phone>
        <website>http://www.allegrochamberorchestra.org/</website>
        <email>info@allegrochamberorchestra.org</email>
        <director>Brian Norcross</director>
        <images>
            <image>http://assets3.razoo.com/assets/media/images/000/017/146/images/size_550x415_razoo%20550x415.png?1297798878</image>
            <image>http://allegrochamberorchestra.org/wp/wp-content/uploads/2013/04/DSC_0757-1024x680.jpg</image>
        </images>
    </organization>
    <organization>
        <id>3005</id>
        <type>opera</type>
        <name>OperaLancaster</name>
        <description>
            OperaLancaster was founded as the Lancaster Opera Workshop in the early 50s in the small in-home studio of 
            Frederick Robinson and Dorothy Darr. Today, OperaLancaster is the only surviving opera company in Pennsylvania 
            between Philaldelphia and Pittsburg producing opera with full sets, costumes, and full orchestra every year.
            Each season, OperaLancaster offers three main stage productions: A light production in English in the Fall, 
            an annual production of Amahl &amp; the Night Visitors in January, and a traditional staged Grand Opera in the 
            Spring. Additionally, OperaLancaster produces and presents smaller concerts, productions, community outreach, 
            lectures, and educational series throughout the year.
        </description>
        <address>
            <street>42 North Prince Street</street>
            <city>Lancaster</city>
            <state>PA</state>
            <zipcode>17603</zipcode>
        </address>
        <phone>717-871.7814</phone>
        <website>http://www.operalancaster.org</website>
        <email>info@operalancaster.org</email>
        <director>William Dewan</director>
        <images>
            <image>https://si0.twimg.com/profile_images/752170165/operalanc.png</image>
        </images>
    </organization>
    <organization>
        <id>3006</id>
        <type>theatre</type>
        <name>PRiMA Theatre Company</name>
        <description>
            We believe that the arts are at their best when they speak your language, jab at the status quo and enrich your life. 
            That is why PRiMA Theatre Company, Lancaster's freshest professional theatre, is beckoning in a new era of relevant 
            and modern arts programming to the Lancaster area. Producing Director, Mitchell M. Nugent leads the non-profit 
            organization in exciting main-stage shows in concert style and energetic, top-notch cabarets at The Ware Center.
        </description>
        <address>
            <street>42 North Prince Street</street>
            <city>Lancaster</city>
            <state>PA</state>
            <zipcode>17603</zipcode>
        </address>
        <phone>717-327-5124</phone>
        <website>http://www.operalancaster.org</website>
        <email>info@operalancaster.org</email>
        <director>Mitchell M. Nugent</director>
        <images>
            <image>http://sphotos-a.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-snc6/p206x206/253436_501960279832044_180804686_n.jpg</image>
        </images>
    </organization>
    <organization>
        <id>3007</id>
        <type>museum</type>
        <name>Demuth Museum</name>
        <description>
            The Demuth Museum is dedicated to developing awareness, understanding and appreciation of the art work and legacy
            of American modernist Charles Demuth. We engage and inspire diverse audiences through an innovative program of
            exhibitions, education, scholarship and collections activities.
        </description>
        <address>
            <street>120 East King Street</street>
            <city>Lancaster</city>
            <state>PA</state>
            <zipcode>17602</zipcode>
        </address>
        <phone>717-299-9940</phone>
        <website>http://www.demuth.org</website>
        <images>
            <image>http://www.demuth.org/_images/live/Mission_250_1.jpg</image>
        </images>
    </organization>
</organizations>
